# **Obada Jasem**

Frontend Developer

# **♣** Profile

Freshly graduated Software Engineer with 2+ years experience in frontend development mainly for mobile and recently web, seeking a challenging job where my abilities could be further developed and utilized to contribute effectively in achieving the organization's goals. I have a good background in Dart, Flutter, and web development. And about 3+ months experience in Android native development with java.

# Employment History

### Frontend Web Developer at Nestech, Syria

September 2021 — Present

- Converted design into high class frontend web applications with the help of quasar framework.
- Engaged with teammates in daily scrum meetings to optimize the development process.
- Helped to overcome deadlines with 3+ responsive high quality web applications.

### Mobile Application Developer at BadinanSoft, Iraq (remote)

December 2020 — September 2021

- Implemented high quality mobile applications with flutter and native android java.
- Handled various technologies such as creating a small node server using Express JS to track the driver location using Socket IO and integrating it with the mobile flutter app.
- Created company-base-package to reuse shared logic and style across different apps to gain more control and flexibility.

## **Mobile Application Developer at Qlevar, Germany (remote)**

July 2020 — August 2021

- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developer.
- Efficiently translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.
- Managed tasks distribution with-in team.

# Side Projects

#### **TasQment**

Mobile app for tasQment an agile-based project management system https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tasqment.tasqment

# Education

Master Of Web Science, Syrian Virtual University

January 2022 — Present

Software Engineering, Tishreen University, Syria

September 2016 — September 2022

#### **Details**

UAE

+971 50 914 8497 obadajasm0@gmail.com

#### Links

Linkedin

Github Twitter

Medium

Protfolio

#### Skills

Dart

Flutter

Bloc & Cubit

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Vue.js

Quasar

Vuex

Git

#### Languages

Arabic

English